{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "I have ___ records as he has.",
      "a": "four times as",
      "b": "four times many",
      "c": "four times as many",
      "d": "four times many as",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Four times as many: number of my records is 4 times in comparison with him",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Learning to play tennis well is not ___ it seems when you are a spectator.",
      "a": "as easy so",
      "b": "so easy as",
      "c": "as easily as",
      "d": "more easy as",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "-So....as is used in negative sentences, while as.... as.... is used in affirmative ones",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "A child in the first grade tends to be ___ all of the other children in his class.",
      "a": "the same old to",
      "b": "the same age than",
      "c": "as old like",
      "d": "the same age as",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- The same age as = as young as",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Perhaps ___ thirty million Indians were living in America when the Europeans arrived.",
      "a": "that many",
      "b": "very many",
      "c": "as many as",
      "d": "many more",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- As many as: a number that is equal to another number",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is not the words that matter _________ the way you say them.",
      "a": "too much as",
      "b": "as far as",
      "c": "not as much as",
      "d": "so much as",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "-So....as is used in negative sentences, while as.... as.... is used in affirmative ones",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Of gold and silver, ___.",
      "a": "the former is much more precious than the latter.",
      "b": "the former is precious than the latter.",
      "c": "the former is the more precious.",
      "d": "the former is more precious than any other thing.",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- The comparative form : Used when two objects or persons are being compared \n+ Structure: Adj (One syllable word) + er than; More + adj (Two-syllable words) + than ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I don't like to ride in a car. \"I think most people prefer riding ___\"",
      "a": "to walking",
      "b": "than walking",
      "c": "more than walking",
      "d": "better than walking",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Prefer something to something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Catherine is as miserable as miserable ___ be.",
      "a": "can",
      "b": "may",
      "c": "will",
      "d": "must",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Can: used to say that something is possible ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I like black coffee so much because the stronger it is, ___.",
      "a": "I like it better",
      "b": "the more I like",
      "c": "the better I like it",
      "d": "I like it more",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- The +(more/less) adj (er)+ the (more/less) adj (er): used to say that if a particular activity increases, another change happens as a result ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The more Jonathan tried to help her, ___ she seemed to appreciate it.",
      "a": "the lesser",
      "b": "less",
      "c": "lesser",
      "d": "the less",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- The +(more/less) adj (er)+ the (more/less) adj (er): used to say that if a particular activity increases, another change happens as a result. ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}